{
    "id": "590e166bbb464b70b474c1747e6e4372",
    "title": "Present Perfect And Present Perfect Continuous Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It ……………………… continuously since morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has been raining",
                "is raining",
                "was raining"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4829ded4f18a45e2bf592d1cdfb7a875"
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………………… them twice, but they ………………… us yet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "visited, did not visit",
                "have been visiting, have not visited",
                "have visited, have not visited"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "867faebd63214786a7a3557472bf17ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… him in a long time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was not meeting",
                "have not met",
                "have not been meeting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "398ddc3a1db94570b36c5bf180ee6035"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children are hungry. They ………………….. in the garden for hours.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are playing",
                "have been playing",
                "were playing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e5cd25b1944849b09f8bdc102dc39872"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………… each other since our school days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knew",
                "have known"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c3bbb837ec6a4bb48da77b14b14eae96"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. you ……………….. the job?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Did, complete",
                "Had, completed",
                "Have, completed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7cc1ea353caa4147aa07a8eab284a0d1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her health ……………………… considerably.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had improved",
                "have improved",
                "has improved"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2963da422f91479a9adfd3c799da6a3a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………….. a permit.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was obtaining",
                "have obtained",
                "has obtained"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5de21de1ee5644efb6c3a15ba53ca45d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Those who ………………….. their work can go home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are finishing",
                "have finished",
                "has finished"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3122544cd4cd49dc9cded4de7756e348"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the fifth time you …………………. that question.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are asking",
                "have asked",
                "have been asking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1153bb07708c4314be88809409e5747c"
        }
    ]
}